Got an Uber today, got in the car, first thing the guy says to me is like, do you mind if I talk to a friend?
And I'm a normal guy, right? So I said, of course.
And thank you for considering me a friend.
We had the best conversation.
So good.
He was speaking Urdu and I responded in English.
It was a beautiful cultural exchange.
He kept doing this.
I'm like, that must be a cultural gesture.
So I did this.
But I'm good.
I've been doing well.
I've been cooking a lot.
So good.
I learned to cook online, right?
But I think it's so special that recipes that used to be passed down from generation to generation.
I think that's so special.
So I got to tell my kids that my grandfather passed me down Jamie Oliver's superfood pasta.
Tell them that Jamie Oliver's a province in China.
We're from the Jamie people.
I've been cooking, I've been eating at other people's houses.
Diversify the portfolio, you know?
I was at a friend's house eating dinner and he cooked this lamb shoulder and it took him two days to cook this lamb shoulder.
And he was bragging about it.
I didn't even know that was something you could brag about.
Like the amount of time it took you to prepare the meal.
But I found it to be quite a good excuse to serve my guests leftovers.
I went, this is a 24-hour stir-fry.
This pizza's been dry-aged for seven days.
Good stuff.
I love food.
I am a foodie. Guilty.
I love food. I love coffee as well.
Big coffee head.
A couple of fans of coffee. Nice.
I love coffee but I reckon coffee culture's gone nuts.
You know what I mean?
Like it's gone too far.
Because there's coffee places everywhere.
Like I saw a coffee place in a rock climbing gym.
I'm like surely that's too far.
There's a coffee place at my local library.
I saw a woman order a triple shot latte.
I'm like what book are you trying to read?
Must be pretty tough.
You know I was getting a coffee from my mechanics and um...
Mechanics are like the last profession that there's no regular retail price.
Right?
Like there's no sign behind them telling you how much it's gonna cost.
You can't just google how much a service is.
Right? It's just numbers swirling around in their minds.
Only they know on any given day how much they're gonna fleece you.
I don't know if you can tell this just by looking at me but I'm not a pushover.
That's not a funny bit.
Got a great deal out of this guy.
Two tyres. $7,000.
He did upsell me though.
I reckon he upsold me.
I don't think I needed the second tyre.
I just went in for a latte.
This mechanic, he kept saying the word roughly.
Right? He's like it's roughly quite a big job.
It's roughly gonna take one to two days.
Like he kept saying the word roughly and he got so in the habit of saying it that he started saying it when he was asking for my details.
He's like roughly what's your phone number?
I'm like if you want a ballpark.
It's about half a billion.
Coffee is too strong.
This stuff it's too, it's too strong.
You know I mean I remember back in the day coffee used to be nice.
You could drink coffee in the morning and go to sleep the same night.
Like you could even drink it at night time.
Like you could whip up a blend 43.
Watch a couple of episodes and then sink into the night, you know.
Nowadays I have a sip of coffee and I get anxiety. And diarrhea.
I see my barista and my guts flinch.
Having a panic attack in the coffee store. I don't know.
There's no drink that's as relaxing as coffee gets you g'd up.
Someone's trying to tell me that was chamomile tea.
But chamomile tea sucks.
Chamomile tea tastes like if water got wet.
Maybe I'm being harsh.
I like, I like the scent of it.
I've been using this new chamomile shampoo.
Relaxing chamomile flavour.
It's good stuff.
I was using it for the first time.
It's going so well.
But then a bit of it got into my eye.
And it stung a lot.
But I was calm throughout the whole thing.
I don't know, I don't understand it.
Because people ask me to meet for a coffee.
They're like, let's go meet for a coffee.
I don't understand that.
Because what I'm hearing is, let's go do a poo-poo.
You know what I mean?
It's a one hour meeting.
We've only got a half an hour of face-to-face time.
We're both painting the toilets for 15 minutes each.
All right, I don't know about that one.
And I was a big, big, foodie during lockdown.
Gained quite a bit of weight.
At the end of lockdown, I had to go to the doctors for something else.
Haemorrhoids.
But at the end of the meeting, he gave me quite a stern warning.
He's like, I'm sorry, but you have to lose five kilos.
If you want to look hot.
He said that.
And I was trying to figure out how to lose the weight.
I was like, going on YouTube.
And there's all these different ideas about weight loss.
And I couldn't figure out what the correct one was.
Because everyone's like, arguing with everyone.
And I found this one guy.
He's called Carnivore MD.
And his whole thing is a meat-only diet.
But he reckons it's true because he's lived as a raw vegan for eight years before that.
So in his lifetime, he's had a balanced diet.
But it's like, I don't know who to trust.
I had to get a personal trainer.
And this personal trainer was like, you got to put down your body goals.
You got to dream big.
He's like, think big. What are your body goals?
And I was like, I would love to gain two foot.
My dream to be five foot five.
I'm good. I'm doing well.
It's a new year near me.
It's Chinese New Year.
You don't hear about a lot of Chinese New Year resolutions.
I'm going to set off more firecrackers this year.
It's Chinese New Year. Just past Year of the Tiger.
I like the zodiacs in the Chinese New Year.
You know how they have all those different zodiacs?
Anyone celebrate Chinese New Year?
Oh, you do? Are you Chinese or other?
I'm mucking about.
I like the zodiacs, but I think some of them, they sound quite offensive in the Western context.
Like I remember when my dad was introducing our family to other people and he'd tell other people our zodiacs.
It sounds so rude.
He'd be like, my wife's a pig. My daughter's a dog. And my son's a rat.
Anyway, they're all born in the Year of the Horse.
It was meant to be a good year, the Year of the Tiger.
It was meant to be a hot one.
It was not off to a good start for me.
Off to a terrible start actually.
First day of the Year of the Tiger, I walked back into my house and I caught my housemate washing her dog with my shampoo.
I couldn't believe it.
It's this relaxing chamomile stuff.
It was good stuff.
It was expensive.
Like it's the best one at the 7-Eleven.
And on the side of the label it was like vegan, organic, no animal testing.
I had to call them up.
I'm like, it's been tested. He really likes it, you know.
He used so much of the shampoo, this guy, you know.
I don't know if you know this but dogs, they got a lot of hair.
If you don't believe me, think about this.
They got bodies. They don't use body wash.
It's all shampoo, you know.
You'd be wasting your time making a body wash for dogs.
They only service this section.
You know how they got that shaved bit.
Some of you don't know about dogging that on me.
But it was a crazy start to the year.
It's not been all bad though.
Some good stuff happening.
A lot happening in the world of television.
There's constantly a show out.
There's always something to watch.
I've been trying to work on segues.
I think that's a good one.
The world of television. There's a lot out there.
I've been watching so much.
I've been watching all the mainstream stuff, right.
That everyone's been watching.
Finished all of that.
Watched one called Drive to Survive.
Not bad.
Got to be in Melbourne during F1 weekend.
Saw a few grand pricks around.
I actually got to go to one of the races.
It was so good.
But they confiscated all my banana peels.
I don't know.
I watched all the mainstream stuff.
Squid Game. I was in that. Played the little girl.
Then I had to start watching the niche stuff.
Because there's nothing else left.
I started watching one called Old People's Home for four-year-olds.
If you don't know what the premise of this show is.
It's a crazy show.
What they do is they pair up these old people.
These old people, they got depression.
And nothing's been able to solve it.
So in a last-ditch attempt.
They pair them up with four-year-olds.
In order to cure them.
A lot of pressure on the four-year-olds.
I mean these kids, they've lived three years of their life.
On the fourth year, TV producers come up to them.
Said, do you want to be a psychologist?
It's kind of crazy.
But I was watching movies as well.
Last movie I watched before the coronavirus.
You guys know what I'm talking about.
Coronavirus pandemic happened.
The last film I watched was one called Uncut Gems.
Saw that in the cinemas.
Blew my mind, this film.
This was amazing.
High-octane Adam Sandler movie.
I was taken aback by this movie.
Beautiful stuff.
As soon as the movie ended.
I'm like, that's the best movie I've ever seen.
I thought that.
And then the credits started to roll.
And I was sitting next to an old lady.
And all she said was.
There's a lot of yelling. "
And normally I wouldn't have said anything.
Like I let people have their opinions.
But the movie, it affected me so much.
That I had to say something, you know.
I turned to her, I was like, I wouldn't have had to if you'd give me some of your popcorn.
Like I asked.
It's me doing the yelling.
I watched that movie Little Women.
Watched it on my iPhone.
Get those women even littler.
It's so small, couldn't believe it.
I'm on the iPhone.
I'm mucking about on there.
I'm always, I'm trying to be ahead of the tech game.
Do you know what I mean?
You have to be one step ahead.
Because you don't know what they're gonna do to you.
I'm trying to be ahead of big tech.
I was like born into the computer era, you know.
I thought I'd be always good with computers.
Like I thought I could do computers forever.
Five years old.
That's the first time I ever went on a computer.
And I was like, I'm good at this.
Like I knew which ads not to click on.
Like which blokes not to talk to.
I was safe on there.
Not an antivirus running on full blast.
I'm like, I'll never get aged out of this.
That was my thought.
I'm 27 years old now.
Like I've already been aged out.
Nowadays I log on to Google Chrome.
It's saying I got 280 compromised passwords.
I'm like, what do you want me to do about it?
I'm not about to change 280 passwords.
I'd rather just change my life.
Like I'll be someone else.
I reckon.
They reckon you got to have a unique password for every website.
I don't even remember my dad's birthday.
And that's my password.
They don't honour passwords anymore either. They don't respect passwords.
I've started to notice that.
That's kind of creeping into society.
This disrespect for passwords.
Because back in the day, you go onto a website.
You type your password in and they'll be like, yeah, we've heard that.
Like we honour that.
Come on in. Explore the possibilities.
They don't honour passwords anymore.
You ever tried logging into your email from someone else's computer?
They don't let you in anymore.
They send you a text.
You got to print that text out.
Get your dad to sign it.
He takes it into the mayor, right?
The mayor shows you nine unique images.
You got to tell him which one's got a street sign in it.
I don't understand the logic behind this.
Because you're telling me, like, a computer hacker.
They've gone to school for three years.
But they don't know what a street sign looks like.
Blows my mind.
At the bottom, like the reason it says, prove you're not a robot.
And it's like, I don't know whether or not I am a robot.
But I know for sure that you are a robot. You are a website.
So what's it to you?
What's this self-hating robot doing guarding this page?
If anything, you should be letting me in.
You should say, prove you are a robot.
It didn't affect me too much, this whole passwords thing.
Until I was living in this share house and it was in a reception dead zone.
You couldn't get any bars of reception in the house.
And what that means was that I couldn't log in to the email, I couldn't get the texts.
It's a nightmare.
I have to walk out of my house to get reception.
By the time I could get one bar of reception, I was already halfway down the street.
Almost at the post office.
I'm like, I may as well send this email as a letter.
Dear father. Thank you so much for the video.
I'm also suspicious of the vaccine.
I mean, I want to get it taken out of me.
I'm just kidding.
I believe whatever you guys believe.
That's good stuff.
I don't know, I'm doing well.
Thanks for asking.
Normally, comedians will wait for like a big laugh or applause break to drink water.
But an opportunity has not yet presented itself.
No, I'm doing good.